clubjenna.com 2007-08-24

# ClubJenna.com - Privacy Policy

As of March 1, 2007

This Privacy Policy (the“Policy”) applies to Club Jenna, Inc.’s (“Club Jenna”) family of websites (the “Sites”).  These include **clubjenna.com; jennajameson.com; ashtonmoore.com; breabennett.com; chanelstjames.com; clubtera.com; krystalsteal.com; clubjesse.com; sophiarossi.com; summerskyes.com; clubstormydaniels.com; clubbrittany.com; brianabanks.com; chloejones.com; realjanine.com** and any other sites at which this Policy appears. It does not apply to other online or offline Club Jenna sites, products or services.

This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it.  We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and changing the “Effective Date” at the top.  We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes.  By using or navigating any of the Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted.  If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit any of the Sites.

**_What kind of information do we collect?_**

When you join the membership portion of any of our Sites, you are asked to provide your name, street address, e-mail address, username and password, credit card number and expiration date and banking information. When you participate in special events such as contests and polls, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail, username and password, telephone number and birth date.  We may also collect information from our online surveys such as age, gender and income level.

When you visit any of our Sites, we automatically collect certain anonymous demographic information about you, including your IP address. We also collect information regarding your use of the Sites through the use of cookies (see below for more about cookies). 

If you choose to post messages on a bulletin board on any of our Sites, we will maintain on the bulletin board such information about you as you choose to disclose. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account. 

**_How do we use your information?_**

We use your information in order to process your credit card payments, to fulfill your orders and/or requests, to facilitate your viewing of our Sites and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and Site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally.

Club Jenna uses your e-mail address to contact you when necessary and to send periodic e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mails to you about services and products offered by us as well as by third party companies in which we think you may be interested. 

We use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information to tailor your experiences at our Sites by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences.  Anonymous demographic information is shared with advertisers and market researchers on an aggregate basis.

We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services.   We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.

Personal information collected on and/or through the Sites is stored and processed in the United States and by using any of the Sites, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**_Do we share the information we collect with third parties?_**

In some cases, we will share information we collect (including personal information and/or anonymous demographic information) with third party companies who may offer products or services in which we believe you may be interested.  We also share this information with third parties with whom we partner to co-promote and administer sweepstakes and contests on our Sites.  In addition, the names and email addresses of subscribers to clubtera.com are shared with Teravision, Inc. 

We may also share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through the Sites. 

We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or other governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of Club Jenna, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**_Is the information submitted in public forums confidential?_**

No. The Sites may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups to our users.  Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information.  Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information, and you do so at your own risk. 

**_Do we use cookies?_**

Yes.  Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on your computer for future access.  The Sites use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our Sites or make a feature work better.  Generally, cookies can be disabled.  However, you must accept cookies in order to navigate the Sites; register for our membership on our Sites and order products from our online store. 

**_Do we use web beacons?_**

Yes.  Some of our Sites may contain electronic images known as “web beacons” or single-pixel gifs that allow us to count visitors to our Sites and deliver co-branded services.  Web beacons collect limited information including cookie number, time and date of a page view and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides.

**_How secure is your information?_**

Club Jenna takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you and to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. Our third party payment processors provide you with a secure web page through which to submit your billing information when you join the membership portion of any of our Sites, and we are not responsible for their handling or use of your information.  Your personally identifiable information is maintained in a reasonably secure manner including storing such information behind firewalls with limited administrative access. 

**_Does this Policy apply to any websites other than the Sites?_**

No. The Sites contain links to other Internet sites, resources and sources of Club Jenna.  By clicking on an ad banner or other link, you will be redirected off the Sites and to third party websites.  Club Jenna is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such sites.  You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of these sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the site administrator or webmaster of that third party website.

**_How do you unsubscribe from Club Jenna emails?_**

All e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe, and you may unsubscribe at any time.  Additionally, we give you the following options for removing your information from our database: 

(1)        Send an email to support@cjidigital.com;

(2)        Select the opt-out link at the bottom of any Club Jenna email and follow the instructions provided; 

(3)        Send mail to the following address: 

**Club Jenna, Inc.  
8390 E. Via De Ventura  
Suite F110 #258  
Scottsdale, AZ 85258**

**_How do you update/correct your information?_**

You may correct or update your personal information by sending us an email at support@cjidigital.com.

**_Got more questions? We can help!_**

Club Jenna recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Sites or your dealings with Club Jenna, please contact us at support@cjidigital.com or by mail at 8390 E. Via De Ventura Suite F110 #258, Scottsdale, AZ 85258.

Please note that persons under the age of 18 are prohibited from viewing our Sites, and Club Jenna does not knowingly collect any personal information from persons under the age of 18.

**YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

California residents who have an established business relationship with Club Jenna may choose to opt out of Club Jenna disclosing personal information about them to third parties for marketing purposes. 

From time to time, we may share your personal information with carefully screened companies that offer products or services that we believe you may enjoy. If you do not want us to share your personal information with such third parties, please send us your name, address and phone number to support@cjidigital.com. 

Your opt out request will be processed within 30 days of the date it was received.
